Now, let's go ahead and download the source code, so for that first, we need to create a Iraq tree.
For that, I will switch back to the terminal and create a direct riposte.
OK, let's get into that.
There are three.
OK.
I am now inside that.
Now, let's configure it.
Username.
OK.
You know, similarly, Kobe said the email.
OK, so I'm done with it, initialization.
So now and the next step is actually to initialize their rapport.
So we are going to download one particular branch, so we should use this second second command.
So I'll just copy this part.
And just pass it over here and our branch.
We are going to pick up a tall branch.
The latest one?
But we should pick it up from this back from here.
So we'll take the latest.
And just based idea and just in time, so it's downloading the and it's basically initializing a repository,
so this will be pretty fast.
And after that, we need to run triple sync, which will actually download the repository.
So I think this will be done in another couple of minutes.
Yeah.
So the rapport is now initialized.
So now you need to just buy rapport sync.
So here you can do you the number of the logical course you have got.
And this is going to take a lot of time.
I guess at least one hour it will take and depending upon your machine and the internet connection,
it's going to take the time accordingly.
So once this is done, we will go ahead and build the rapport.
So that will again take another hour and a half hour, I guess.
So in total, you would need at least three to four hours to to download the source and build it.
OK.